A.D.
Due to its
declining
birthrate
of the
human
popula-
tion,
this
country
has turned
into
a nation
of cats.
Cat Country Japan.
Kinako and Kitty Cat
Kinako, I'm home!
Tadaa! I brought a kitty cat!
A-A kitty?
I brought a stray kitty home
yesterday, you see.
A kitten, you say?
Yep.
I see.
How should I say it? I gave the kitten
too much attention and she...
...ended up like that.
Kinako!
Hmph.
Hmph!
Kinako!
Hmph!!
Hahaha… what should I do?
You have no choice but to spoil her.
Spoil her?
Cats love to be spoiled.
I see.
Hey, there, there.
Want a snack, Kinako?
Slurp, slurp.
I see.
Mugishima… Mugishima!
I like to be spoiled too, you know.
There, there. Rustle, rustle.
Her mood has improved.
I made you all worry.
The new kitten was so cute,
I felt like my reign was coming to an end.
But it looks like I'll be fine.
R-Reign...?
I'm home.
Welcome back!!!
You…!
TL
TM
TS
MX-QC
AI Transcribe was utilized
: geckyzz