A.D.
Due to its
declining
birthrate
of the
human
popula-
tion,
this
country
has turned
into
a nation
of cats.
Cat Country Japan.
Signs of Happiness
When cats are happy,
they show it in various ways.
Like purring, or raising their tail.
That's right.
Mugishima is...
Huh? Mugishima?
What happens when she's happy?
Ohh, so you want
to make Mugishima happy.
Yes.
I see.
In that case...
If you do something
that makes you happy,
maybe she'll be happy too?
Oh, I see.
When it comes down to it,
you should just strike a weird pose.
Humans are happy
just seeing cats in weird poses.
Hmm, I see.
Mugishima?
Yes?
Something that makes me happy.
The throat-petting thing.
What is it?
Ah, Sora, could you put this on?
Hm? What is it?
This is?
It's a present.
Because it's been getting cold lately.
Thank you very much.
It matches yours, Mugishima.
Yeah, it looks good.
Oh my, Mugishima looks happy.
Humans get happy over weird poses.
I'll strike a funny pose, too.
Mhmm, mhmm, just like that.
TL
TM
TS
MX-QC
AI Transcribe was utilized
: geckyzz